so let's see an example of when does it
really matter let's look at a
multi-processor that has coherent memory
but out of order cores
and specifically the core can predict a
branch and later verify that it was
taken or not taken correctly the store
instructions in each core are done
strictly in program order so it doesn't
reorder any stores but the loads between
stored instructions can be reordered on
a core now let's say that we have core 1
and core 2 where core 1 executes the
following code while a flag is 0 it
waits
and then it prints data while core 2
writes 10 to data
then increments data by 5 then sets the
flag and let's say that both flag and
data are 0 initially before core 2 gets
to change them so now core 1 when it
prints the data what are the values that
it can possibly print can it print 0
can it print 5
can it print 10
can it print 15
and can it print anything else